Guide to the Texas Monthly Editorial Records
The Wittliff Collections
- Issue files, 1976-2017
  - 2001
    - 2001, June (Box 823)
    - 2001, July (Box 671)
    - 2001, July (Box 686)
    - 2001, July (Box 687)
    - 2001, July (Box 688)
    - 2001, August (Box 688)
    - 2001, August (Box 689)
    - 2001, August (Box 690)
    - 2001, August (Box 695)
    - 2001, September (Box 690)
    - 2001, September (Box 691)
    - 2001, September (Box 722)
    - 2001, October (Box 689)
    - 2001, October (Box 692)
    - 2001, October (Box 693)
    - 2001, October (Box 695)
    - 2001, October (Box 722)
    - 2001, November (Box 692)
    - 2001, November (Box 693)
    - 2001, November (Box 694)
    - 2001, November (Box 695)
    - 2001, December (Box 695)
    - 2001, December (Box 696)
  - 2002
    - 2002, January (Box 696)
    - 2002, January (Box 697)
    - 2002, January (Box 699)
    - 2002, February (Box 697)
    - 2002, February, Box 698 conains VHS, cassettes (Box 698)
    - 2002, February (Box 823)
    - 2002, March, Box 698 conains VHS, cassettes (Box 698)
    - 2002, March (Box 699)
    - 2002, April (Box 699)
    - 2002, April (Box 700)
    - 2002, April (Box 701)
    - 2002, April (Box 823)
    - 2002, May (Box 701)
    - 2002, May (Box 702)
    - 2002, June (Box 702)
    - 2002, June (Box 703)
    - 2002, June (Box 704)
    - 2002, June (Box 705)
    - 2002, July (Box 703)
    - 2002, July (Box 704)
    - 2002, July (Box 705)
    - 2002, August (Box 706)
    - 2002, August, Box 707 contains a VHS (Box 707)
    - 2002, September, Box 707 contains a VHS (Box 707)
    - 2002, September (Box 708)
    - 2002, October (Box 708)
    - 2002, October (Box 709)
    - 2002, November (Box 709)
    - 2002, November, Box 710 contains 3 Books (Box 710)
    - 2002, December, Box 710 contains 3 Books (Box 710)
    - 2002, December (Box 826)
      2007-108
    - 2002, December (Box 827)
  - 2003
    - 2003, January (Box 873)
    - 2003, January (Box 877)
    - 2003, February, Box 878 contains 68 Photos with negatives & a book (Box 878)
    - 2003, March, Box 878 contains 68 Photos with negatives & a book (Box 878)
    - 2003, March, Box 879 contains 3 color slides (Box 879)
    - 2003, April, Box 879 contains 3 color slides (Box 879)
    - 2003, May (Box 880)
    - 2003, May (Box 881)
    - 2003, June (Box 880)
    - 2003, June (Box 881)
    - 2003, June (Box 882)
    - 2003, July (Box 882)
    - 2003, July (Box 883)
    - 2003, August (Box 883)
    - 2003, August, Box 884 contains 18 Microcassettes (Box 884)
    - 2003, August, Box 885 contains a book (Box 885)
    - 2003, September, Box 885 contains a book (Box 885)
    - 2003, September (Box 886)
    - 2003, October (Box 886)
    - 2003, October (Box 887)
    - 2003, October (Box 888)
    - 2003, November (Box 888)
    - 2003, November (Box 889)
    - 2003, December (Box 889)
    - 2003, December (Box 891)
  - 2004
    - 2004, January (Box 890)
    - 2004, January (Box 823)
    - 2004, January (Box 891)
    - 2004, February (Box 823)
    - 2004, February (Box 890)
    - 2004, March (Box 898)
    - 2004, March (Box 899)
    - 2004, April (Box 899)
    - 2004, April (Box 900)
    - 2004, April (Box 901)
    - 2004, May (Box 900)
    - 2004, May (Box 901)
    - 2004, May (Box 905)
    - 2004, June (Box 905)
    - 2004, June (Box 906)
    - 2004, June (Box 907)
    - 2004, July (Box 907)
    - 2004, July (Box 908)
    - 2004, August (Box 908)
    - 2004, August (Box 909)
    - 2004, September (Box 909)
    - 2004, September (Box 910)
    - 2004, September (Box 913)
    - 2004, September (Box 914)
    - 2004, October (Box 910)
    - 2004, October (Box 913)
    - 2004, October (Box 914)
    - 2004, November (Box 913)
    - 2004, November (Box 915)
    - 2004, November (Box 916)
    - 2004, December (Box 917)
    - 2004, December (Box 918)
    - 2004, December (Box 930)
  - 2005
    - 2005, January (Box 930)
    - 2005, January (Box 931)
    - 2005, February (Box 932)
    - 2005, February (Box 933)
    - 2005, March (Box 857)
    - 2005, March (Box 932)
    - 2005, March (Box 933)
    - 2005, April (Box 822)
    - 2005, April (Box 823)
    - 2005, April (Box 934)
    - 2005, April (Box 935)
    - 2005, April, Box 1037 contains a microcassette (Box 1037)
      2011-143
    - 2005, May (Box 934)
    - 2005, May (Box 935)
    - 2005, May (Box 936)
    - 2005, June (Box 936)
    - 2005, June (Box 937)
    - 2005, July (Box 936)
    - 2005, July (Box 937)
    - 2005, July (Box 938)
    - 2005, July (Box 939)
    - 2005, August (Box 939)
    - 2005, August (Box 940)
    - 2005, August (Box 941)
    - 2005, September (Box 941)
    - 2005, September (Box 942)
    - 2005, September (Box 943)
    - 2005, October (Box 864)
    - 2005, October (Box 946)
    - 2005, October (Box 947)
    - 2005, November (Box 946)
    - 2005, November (Box 947)
    - 2005, November (Box 950)
    - 2005, November (Box 951)
    - 2005, December (Box 823)
    - 2005, December (Box 950)
    - 2005, December (Box 951)
    - 2000, December (Box 657)
    - 1995, December (Box 220)
    - 2000, July (Box 646)
    - 2000, July (Box 648)
    - 2000, August (Box 648)
    - 2000, August (Box 649)
    - 2000, August (Box 675)
    - 2000, October (Box 655)
    - 2000, November (Box 654)
    - 2000, November (Box 655)
    - 2000, November (Box 657)
    - 2000, December (Box 654)
    - 2000, December (Box 656)
  - 2006
    - 2006, January (Box 951)
    - 2006, January (Box 954)
    - 2006, February (Box 981)
    - 2006, February (Box 982)
    - 2006, March (Box 983)
    - 2006, March (Box 984)
    - 2006, March (Box 981)
    - 2006, March (Box 982)
    - 2006, April (Box 984)
    - 2006, April (Box 985)
    - 2006, April (Box 986)
    - 2006, May (Box 985)
    - 2006, May (Box 986)
    - 2006, May (Box 987)
    - 2006, May (Box 988)
    - 2006, June (Box 987)
    - 2006, June (Box 988)
    - 2006, June (Box 990)
    - 2006, July (Box 989)
    - 2006, July (Box 990)
    - 2006, August (Box 989)
    - 2006, August (Box 992)
    - 2006, September (Box 991)
    - 2006, September (Box 992)
    - 2006, September (Box 993)
    - 2006, September (Box 994)
    - 2006, October (Box 993)
    - 2006, October (Box 994)
    - 2006, October (Box 996)
    - 2006, November (Box 995)
    - 2006, November (Box 996)
    - 2006, December (Box 995)
    - 2006, December (Box 998)
    - 2006, December, Box 1037 contains a microcassette (Box 1037)
  - 2007
    - 2007, January (Box 997)
    - 2007, January (Box 998)
    - 2007, January (Box 999)
    - 2007, February (Box 999)
    - 2007, February (Box 1000)
    - 2007, February (Box 1001)
    - 2007, March (Box 1001)
    - 2007, March (Box 1002)
    - 2007, April (Box 1002)
    - 2007, April (Box 1003)
    - 2007, April (Box 1004)
    - 2007, April (Box 1005)
    - 2007, May (Box 1003)
    - 2007, May (Box 1004)
    - 2007, May (Box 1005)
    - 2007, May (Box 1007)
    - 2007, June (Box 1005)
    - 2007, June (Box 1006)
    - 2007, June (Box 1007)
    - 2007, June, Box 1037 contains a microcassette (Box 1037)
    - 2007, July (Box 1007)
    - 2007, July (Box 1008)
    - 2007, August (Box 1008)
    - 2007, August (Box 1009)
    - 2007, September (Box 1009)
    - 2007, September (Box 1010)
    - 2007, September (Box 1011)
    - 2007, October (Box 1012)
    - 2007, October (Box 1013)
    - 2007, November (Box 1014)
    - 2007, November (Box 1015)
    - 2007, December (Box 1015)
    - 2007, December (Box 1016)
    - 2007, December (Box 1017)
  - 2008
    - 2008, January (Box 1017)
    - 2008, January (Box 1020)
    - 2008, January (Box 1021)
    - 2008, January, Box 1023 contains 1 DVD, 3 audiocassettes (Box 1023)
    - 2008, February (Box 1020)
    - 2008, February (Box 1021)
    - 2008, February, Box 1023 contains 1 DVD, 3 audiocassettes (Box 1023)
    - 2008, March, Box 1023 contains 1 DVD, 3 audiocassettes (Box 1023)
    - 2008, March (Box 1025)
    - 2008, April (Box 1016)
    - 2008, April (Box 1022)
    - 2008, May (Box 1016)
    - 2008, May (Box 1027)
    - 2008, May (Box 1028)
    - 2008, June (Box 1025)
    - 2008, June (Box 1026)
    - 2008, June (Box 1028)
    - 2008, June (Box 1029)
    - 2008, July (Box 1025)
    - 2008, July (Box 1026)
    - 2008, July (Box 1030)
    - 2008, August (Box 1026)
    - 2008, August (Box 1030)
    - 2008, August (Box 1031)
    - 2008, September (Box 1027)
    - 2008, September (Box 1031)
    - 2008, October (Box 1015)
    - 2008, October (Box 1032)
    - 2008, November (Box 1010)
    - 2008, November (Box 1011)
    - 2008, November (Box 1032)
    - 2008, November (Box 1033)
    - 2008, December (Box 1014)
    - 2008, December (Box 1033)
  - 2009
    - 2009, January (Box 1013)
    - 2009, January (Box 1034)
    - 2009, February (Box 1034)
    - 2009, March (Box 1035)
    - 2009, April (Box 1020)
    - 2009, April (Box 1030)
    - 2009, April (Box 1035)
    - 2009, April (Box 1036)
    - 2009, May (Box 1030)
    - 2009, May (Box 1036)
    - 2009, June (Box 1065)
    - 2009, July (Box 1065)
    - 2009, July (Box 1066)
    - 2009, August (Box 1066)
    - 2009, August (Box 1067)
    - 2009, September (Box 1067)
    - 2009, September (Box 1125)
      2014-080
    - 2009, September (Box 1139)
    - 2009, October (Box 1125)
    - 2009, October (Box 1126)
    - 2009, November (Box 1126)
    - 2009, November (Box 1127)
    - 2009, December (Box 1127)
    - 2009, December (Box 1128)
  - 2010
    - 2010, January (Box 1128)
    - 2010, January (Box 1129)
    - 2010, February (Box 1130)
    - 2010, February (Box 1131)
    - 2010, February (Box 1131)
    - 2010, March (Box 1132)
    - 2010, March (Box 1133)
    - 2010, April (Box 1133)
    - 2010, April (Box 1134)
    - 2010, May (Box 1134)
    - 2010, May (Box 1135)
    - 2010, June (Box 1135)
    - 2010, June (Box 1136)
    - 2010, July (Box 1136)
    - 2010, July (Box 1137)
    - 2010, August (Box 1138)
    - 2010, September (Box 1139)
    - 2010, October (Box 1152)
      2016-114
    - 2010, October (Box 1153)
    - 2010, October (Box 1154)
    - 2010, October (Box 1155)
    - 2010, November (Box 1156)
    - 2010, November (Box 1157)
    - 2010, December (Box 1156)
    - 2010, December (Box 1157)
  - 2011
    - 2011, January (Box 1158)
    - 2011, February (Box 1158)
    - 2011, February (Box 1159)
    - 2011, March (Box 1160)
    - 2011, March (Box 1161)
    - 2011, April (Box 1162)
    - 2011, April (Box 1163)
    - 2011, May (Box 1163)
    - 2011, May (Box 1164)
    - 2011, June (Box 1164)
    - 2011, July (Box 1164)
    - 2011, July (Box 1165)
    - 2011, August (Box 1166)
    - 2011, September (Box 1166)
    - 2011, September (Box 1167)
    - 2011, October (Box 1168)
    - 2011, November (Box 1169)
    - 2011, November (Box 1170)
    - 2011, December (Box 1170)
    - 2011, December (Box 1171)
  - 2012
    - 2012, January (Box 1171)
    - 2012, January (Box 1172)
    - 2012, February (Box 1173)
    - 2012, March (Box 1174)
    - 2012, April (Box 1175)
    - 2012, May (Box 1176)
    - 2012, June (Box 1177)
    - 2012, June (Box 1178)
    - 2012, July (Box 1178)
    - 2012, August (Box 1178)
    - 2012, August (Box 1179)
    - 2012, August (Box 1180)
    - 2012, September (Box 1180)
    - 2012, October (Box 1180)
    - 2012, October (Box 1181)
    - 2012, November (Box 1181)
    - 2012, December (Box 1182)
    - 2012, December (Box 1183)
    - 2012, December (Box 1184)
  - 2013
    - 2013, January (Box 1185)
    - 2013, February (Box 1185)
    - 2013, February (Box 1187)
    - 2013, March (Box 1186)
    - 2013, March (Box 1187)
    - 2013, March (Box 1188)
    - 2013, April (Box 1186)
    - 2013, April (Box 1188)
    - 2013, May (Box 1186)
    - 2013, May (Box 1188)
    - 2013, June (Box 1186)
    - 2013, June (Box 1189)
    - 2013, July (Box 1189)
    - 2013, July (Box 1190)
    - 2013, August (Box 1190)
    - 2013, September (Box 1190)
    - 2013, September (Box 1191)
    - 2013, October (Box 1191)
    - 2013, October (Box 1202)
      2017-085
    - 2013, November (Box 1203)
    - 2013, December (Box 1203)
  - 2014
    - 2014, January (Box 1204)
    - 2014, February (Box 1204)
    - 2014, February (Box 1205)
    - 2014, March (Box 1205)
    - 2014, March (Box 1206)
    - 2014, April (Box 1206)
    - 2014, April (Box 1207)
    - 2014, April (Box 1208)
    - 2014, April (Box 1209)
    - 2014, April (Box 1210)
    - 2014, May (Box 1210)
    - 2014, June (Box 1210)
    - 2014, June (Box 1211)
    - 2014, July (Box 1211)
    - 2014, July (Box 1212)
    - 2014, August (Box 1212)
    - 2014, August (Box 1213)
    - 2014, September (Box 1213)
    - 2014, September (Box 1214)
    - 2014, October (Box 1214)
    - 2014, November (Box 1214)
    - 2014, November (Box 1215)
    - 2014, November (Box 1216)
    - 2014, December (Box 1216)
    - 2014, December (Box 1217)
  - 2015
    - 2015, January (Box 1217)
    - 2015, January (Box 1218)
    - 2015, February (Box 1219)
    - 2015, March (Box 1219)
    - 2015, March (Box 1220)
    - 2015, April (Box 1220)
    - 2015, April (Box 1221)
    - 2015, May (Box 1222)
    - 2015, June (Box 1222)
    - 2015, June (Box 1223)
    - 2015, July (Box 1223)
    - 2015, July (Box 1224)
    - 2015, August (Box 1224)
    - 2015, August (Box 1225)
    - 2015, September (Box 1225)
    - 2015, September (Box 1255)
      2020-096
    - 2015, October (Box 1226)
    - 2015, November (Box 1226)
    - 2015, November (Box 1227)
    - 2015, December (Box 1227)
    - 2015, December (Box 1228)
  - 2016
    - 2016, January (Box 1228)
    - 2016, January (Box 1229)
    - 2016, February (Box 1229)
    - 2016, February (Box 1230)
    - 2016, March (Box 1230)
    - 2016, March (Box 1231)
    - 2016, April (Box 1231)
    - 2016, May (Box 1231)
    - 2016, June (Box 1231)
    - 2016, July (Box 1231)
    - 2016, August (Box 1231)
    - 2016, September (Box 1232)
    - 2016, October (Box 1232)
    - 2016, November (Box 1232)
    - 2016, December (Box 1232)
    - 2016, December (Box 1255)
  - 2017
    - 2017, January (Box 1232)
    - 2017, January (Box 1233)
    - 2017, February (Box 1233)
    - 2017, March (Box 1233)
    - 2017, March (Box 1252)
    - 2017, April (Box 1252)
    - 2017, May (Box 1252)
    - 2017, June (Box 1252)
    - 2017, July (Box 1252)
    - 2017, August (Box 1253)
    - 2017, September (Box 1253)
    - 2017, October (Box 1253)
    - 2017, November (Box 1253)
    - 2017, December (Box 1253)
  - 2018
    - 2018, January (Box 1254)
    - 2018, February (Box 1254)
    - 2018, March (Box 1254)
    - 2018, April (Box 1254)
    - 2018, May (Box 1255)
- Nate Blakeslee
  - 2006, September (Box 1042)
  - 2006, September (Box 1043)
  - 2007, March (Box 1042)
  - 2007, March (Box 1043)
  - 2007, May (Box 1042)
  - 2007, August (Box 1042)
  - 2007, August (Box 1043)
  - 2007, December (Box 1042)
  - 2008, February (Box 1042)
  - 2008, October (Box 1042)
- Paul Burka
  - Manges Material, circa 1984 (Box 082B/083A)
  - Manges Material, circa 1984 (Box 082A)
  - Story notes, circa 1988 (Box 144C/145A)
  - Story notes, circa 1988 (Box 145B)
  - Story notes, circa 1989 (Box 151C/152A)
  - Story notes, circa 1989 (Box 152B)
  - Story notes, circa 1989 (Box 152C/153A)
- Gary Cartwright
  - 2004, April (Box 978)
  - 2004, April (Box 979)
- Pamela Colloff
  - 1997, October (Box 974)
  - 1997, November (Box 974)
  - 1997, December (Box 974)
  - 1998, January (Box 974)
  - 1998, January (Box 975)
  - 1998, May (Box 972)
  - 1998, November (Box 972)
  - 1999, January (Box 974)
  - 1999, January (Box 975)
  - 1999, February (Box 973)
  - 1999, June (Box 975)
  - 1999, August (Box 975)
  - 1999, August (Box 973)
  - 1999, November (Box 973)
  - 1999, December (Box 973)
  - 2000, March (Box 975)
  - 2000, April (Box 973)
  - 2000, August (Box 970)
  - 2000, August (Box 968)
  - 2001, 2003 (Box 967)
  - 2001, 2003 (Box 966)
  - 2001, April (Box 970)
  - 2001, April (Box 969)
  - 2002, April (Box 968)
  - 2002, July (Box 968)
  - 2002, November (Box 968)
  - 2003, December (Box 970)
  - 2003, December (Box 971)
  - 2003, December (Box 1048)
  - 2005, April (Box 1047)
  - 2005, June (Box 1046)
  - 2006, August (Box 1048)
  - 2007, February (Box 1046)
  - 2007, August (Box 1048)
  - 2007, September (Box 1046)
  - 2008, December (Box 1048)
  - 2009, January (Box 1046)
  - 2009, June (Box 1048)
  - 1998; 2000-2002 (Box 1234)
  - 1999, March (Box 961)
  - 2000, June (Box 960)
  - 2001, January (Box 960)
  - 2001, April (Box 961)
  - 2001, September (Box 961)
  - 2002, July (Box 961)
  - 2003, January (Box 961)
  - 2003, April (Box 960)
  - 2003, August (Box 957)
  - 2003, October (Box 964)
  - 2003, December (Box 958)
  - 2004, October (Box 1059)
  - 2004, November (Box 1059)
  - 2004, November (Box 1054)
  - 2004, November (Box 1055)
  - 2005, March (Box 965)
  - 2005, June (Box 964)
  - 2005, July (Box 1057)
  - 2005, September (Box 965)
  - 2005, December (Box 965)
  - 2006, January (Box 1055)
  - 2006, January (Box 1058)
  - 2006, March (Box 963)
  - 2006, July (Box 962)
  - 2006, October (Box 1053)
  - 2006, October (Box 963)
  - 2006, October (Box 962)
  - 2007, January (Box 963)
  - 2007, February (Box 962)
  - 2007, June (Box 1056)
  - 2007, September (Box 1056)
  - 2007, October (Box 1056)
  - 2008, January (Box 1056)
  - 2008, May (Box 1056)
  - 2008, September (Box 1057)
  - 2008, September (Box 1060)
  - 2008, November (Box 1056)
  - 2009, February (Box 1058)
  - 2009, April (Box 1076)
  - 2009, May (Box 1077)
  - 2009, August (Box 1060)
  - 2009, October (Box 1077)
  - 2010, March (Box 1077)
  - 2010, April (Box 1077)
  - 2010, May (Box 1075)
  - 2010, July (Box 1076)
  - 2010, September (Box 1077)
  - 2010, November (Box 1077)
  - 2010, December (Box 1077)
  - 2011 (Box 1237)
  - 2011-2015 (Box 1238)
  - 2012-2013; 2015-2016 (Box 1239)
  - 2012-2013; 2015-2016 (Box 1240)
  - 2012, 2016-2017 (Box 1236)
  - Kerry Max Cook, 2012 and 2017 (Box 1241)
  - Kerry Max Cook, 2012 and 2017 (Box 1242)
  - Kerry Max Cook, 2012 and 2017 (Box 1243)
  - Lake Waco, 2014 (Box 1244)
  - Lake Waco, 2014 (Box 1245)
  - undated (Box 959)
- Skip Hollandsworth
  - circa 1989 (Box 464)
  - 1993, May (Box 537)
  - 2007, July (Box 1024)
  - 2008, August (Box 1079)
- Pat Sharpe
  - 1987, 2014-2015 (Box 1249)
  - 1988, June (Box 1039)
  - 1991, June (Box 1039)
  - 1995, September (Box 1039)
  - 1998, 2008 (Box 1246)
  - 1999, March (Box 1039)
  - 2001-2006, 2008 (Box 1038)
  - 2003 (Box 1039)
  - 2004 (Box 1039)
  - 2004, July (Box 1040)
  - 2006, November (Box 1039)
  - 2006, December (Box 1039)
  - 2007, December (Box 1040)
  - 2009-2011 (Box 1247)
  - 2013, 2016-2017 (Box 1248)
  - 2014, 2016, 2018 (Box 1250)
  - 2016-2017 (Box 1251)
- Katy Vine
  - 2001, August (Box 1045)
  - 2002, August (Box 1045)
  - 2002, September (Box 1051)
  - 2003, January (Box 1051)
  - 2003, August (Box 1051)
  - 2004, January (Box 1051)
  - 2004, July (Box 1051)
  - 2005, October (Box 1051)
  - 2006, January (Box 1051)
  - 2006, April (Box 1051)
  - 2006, November (Box 1041)
  - 2007, February (Box 1051)
  - 2007, March (Box 1051)
  - 2007, May (Box 1051)
  - 2007, July (Box 1051)
  - 2007, November (Box 1044)
  - 2008, May (Box 1044)
  - 2008, August (Box 1045)
  - 2008, October (Box 1045)
  - 2008, October (Box 1044)
  - 2009, May (Box 1045)
  - 2009, June (Box 1045)
  - 2009, October (Box 1149)
  - 2009, October (Box 1150)
  - 2009, October (Box 1151)
  - 2010-2014 (Box 1192)
  - 2010-2014 (Box 1193)
- Other Editorial Files
  - Dead Stories, 1983-1984 (Box 071B)
  - Dead Stories, 1985-1986 (Box 096C/097A)
  - Dead Stories, 1988-1989 (Box 334)
  - Editorial Assistant "Reader Files", 2005-2008 (Box 1112)
  - Editorial Assistant "Reader Files", 2007 (Box 1113)
  - Editorial Assistant "Reader Files", 2007 (Box 1114)
  - Editorial Assistant "Reader Files", 2008 (Box 1111)
  - Editorial Correspondence, 1990-1992 (Box 790)
  - Editorial FIles, January, 2001 (Box 662)
  - Editorial FIles, February, 2001 (Box 662)
  - Editorial FIles, March, 2001 (Box 662)
  - Fact Files, 2006-2008 (Box 1122)
  - General, 1995-1996 (Box 599)
  - General, 1995-1996 (Box 601)
  - Legal, December, 1997 (Box 770)
  - Legal, January, 1998 (Box 770)
  - Legal, January, 1998 (Box 769)
  - Legal, February, 1998 (Box 769)
  - Legal, January, 1999 (Box 785)
  - Reprints, 1992-2002 (Box 724)
  - Research, 1998-2000 (Box 608)
  - Research, 1998-2000 (Box 609)
  - Story Files, 1988-1992 (Box 474)
  - Story Files, 1988-1992 (Box 475)
  - Trammell Crow, circa 1984 (Box 089C/090A)